let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 21,
    "question": "Captive breeding is an example of",
    "answer": "ex-situ conservation",
    "options": [
      "in-situ conservation",
      "ex-situ conservation",
      "in-situ preservation",
      "ex-situ preservation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 22,
    "question": "The \"subset of physical and biotic environmental factors that permit an animal (or plant) or survive and reproduce\" is the definition of",
    "answer": "habitat",
    "options": [
      "habitat",
      "ecosystem",
      "biome",
      "biosphere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 23,
    "question": "We prefer those areas for the creation of a conservation reserve where the level of threat is",
    "answer": "medium",
    "options": [
      "very high",
      "medium",
      "very low",
      "non-existent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 24,
    "question": "Which of these is a deterministic factor",
    "answer": "death rate",
    "options": [
      "environmental variation",
      "forest fire",
      "death rate",
      "diseases"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 25,
    "question": "The acronym HIPPO does not include",
    "answer": "habitat enhancement",
    "options": [
      "habitat loss",
      "habitat enhancement",
      "invasive species",
      "human overpopulation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 26,
    "question": "Which of these correctly represents the process of habitat fragmentation and loss",
    "answer": "original forest --> dissection --> perforation --> fragmentation --> attrition",
    "options": [
      "original forest --> dissection --> attrition --> fragmentation --> perforation",
      "original forest --> dissection --> perforation --> attrition --> fragmentation",
      "original forest --> dissection --> fragmentation --> perforation --> attrition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 27,
    "question": "The acronym HIPPO does not include",
    "answer": "pollination",
    "options": [
      "habitat loss",
      "invasive species",
      "pollination",
      "pollution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 28,
    "question": "Which of these is a stochastic factor",
    "answer": "environmental fluctuations",
    "options": [
      "birth rate",
      "death rate",
      "population structures",
      "environmental fluctuations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 29,
    "question": "According to Leopold, which of these in not a tool of habitat management",
    "answer": "sickle",
    "options": [
      "fire",
      "gun",
      "cattle",
      "sickle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 30,
    "question": "Zoo is an example of",
    "answer": "ex-situ conservation",
    "options": [
      "in-situ conservation",
      "ex-situ conservation",
      "in-situ preservation",
      "ex-situ preservation"
    ]
  }]